Preparing twitter database
Database ready
New User "newuser" is registered
"newuser": "user1" is added
"newuser": "user2" is added
"newuser": "user3" is added
"newuser": "user4" is added
"newuser": "user5" is added
"newuser": Logged Out. Log Session time is 12 milliseconds
"user1": Logged in. Got 0 tweets.
"user1": Tweet sent to 0 logged in subscribers
"user2": Logged in. Got 0 tweets.
"user2": Tweet sent to 0 logged in subscribers
"user3": Logged in. Got 3 tweets.
"user3": Tweet sent to 0 logged in subscribers
"user4": Logged in. Got 2 tweets.
"user4": Tweet sent to 2 logged in subscribers
"user5": Logged in. Got 2 tweets.
"user5": Tweet sent to 2 logged in subscribers
"user6": Logged in. Got 6 tweets.
"user6": Tweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user7": Logged in. Got 9 tweets.
"user7": Tweet sent to 11 logged in subscribers
"user8": Logged in. Got 6 tweets.
"user8": Tweet sent to 7 logged in subscribers
"user9": Logged in. Got 9 tweets.
"user9": Tweet sent to 11 logged in subscribers
"user10": Logged in. Got 7 tweets.
"user10": Tweet sent to 5 logged in subscribers
"user11": Logged in. Got 8 tweets.
"user11": Tweet sent to 9 logged in subscribers
"user12": Logged in. Got 2 tweets.
"user12": Tweet sent to 7 logged in subscribers
"user13": Logged in. Got 14 tweets.
"user14": Logged in. Got 7 tweets.
"user13": Tweet sent to 7 logged in subscribers
"user14": Tweet sent to 11 logged in subscribers
"user15": Logged in. Got 14 tweets.
"user15": Tweet sent to 4 logged in subscribers
"user16": Logged in. Got 10 tweets.
"user16": Tweet sent to 4 logged in subscribers
"user17": Logged in. Got 6 tweets.
"user17": Tweet sent to 8 logged in subscribers
"user18": Logged in. Got 12 tweets.
"user18": Tweet sent to 9 logged in subscribers
"user19": Logged in. Got 8 tweets.
"user19": Tweet sent to 7 logged in subscribers
"user20": Logged in. Got 15 tweets.
"user20": Tweet sent to 5 logged in subscribers
"user21": Logged in. Got 3 tweets.
"user21": Tweet sent to 5 logged in subscribers
"user22": Logged in. Got 13 tweets.
"user22": Tweet sent to 8 logged in subscribers
"user23": Logged in. Got 16 tweets.
"user23": Tweet sent to 7 logged in subscribers
"user24": Logged in. Got 8 tweets.
"user24": Tweet sent to 9 logged in subscribers
"user25": Logged in. Got 11 tweets.
"user25": Tweet sent to 4 logged in subscribers
"user26": Logged in. Got 12 tweets.
"user26": Tweet sent to 5 logged in subscribers
"user27": Logged in. Got 17 tweets.
"user27": Tweet sent to 6 logged in subscribers
"user28": Logged in. Got 11 tweets.
"user28": Tweet sent to 4 logged in subscribers
"user29": Logged in. Got 20 tweets.
"user29": Tweet sent to 6 logged in subscribers
"user30": Logged in. Got 17 tweets.
"user30": Tweet sent to 5 logged in subscribers
"user31": Logged in. Got 19 tweets.
"user31": Tweet sent to 4 logged in subscribers
"user32": Logged in. Got 16 tweets.
"user32": Tweet sent to 5 logged in subscribers
"user33": Logged in. Got 19 tweets.
"user33": Tweet sent to 6 logged in subscribers
"user34": Logged in. Got 24 tweets.
"user34": Tweet sent to 6 logged in subscribers
"user35": Logged in. Got 16 tweets.
"user35": Tweet sent to 7 logged in subscribers
"user36": Logged in. Got 16 tweets.
"user36": Tweet sent to 8 logged in subscribers
"user37": Logged in. Got 14 tweets.
"user37": Tweet sent to 4 logged in subscribers
"user38": Logged in. Got 24 tweets.
"user38": Tweet sent to 7 logged in subscribers
"user39": Logged in. Got 22 tweets.
"user39": Tweet sent to 6 logged in subscribers
"user40": Logged in. Got 18 tweets.
"user40": Tweet sent to 3 logged in subscribers
"user41": Logged in. Got 10 tweets.
"user41": Tweet sent to 4 logged in subscribers
"user42": Logged in. Got 19 tweets.
"user42": Tweet sent to 5 logged in subscribers
"user43": Logged in. Got 16 tweets.
"user43": Tweet sent to 5 logged in subscribers
"user44": Logged in. Got 17 tweets.
"user44": Tweet sent to 2 logged in subscribers
"user45": Logged in. Got 21 tweets.
"user45": Tweet sent to 5 logged in subscribers
"user46": Logged in. Got 19 tweets.
"user46": Tweet sent to 6 logged in subscribers
"user47": Logged in. Got 18 tweets.
"user47": Tweet sent to 2 logged in subscribers
"user48": Logged in. Got 22 tweets.
"user48": Tweet sent to 2 logged in subscribers
"user49": Logged in. Got 21 tweets.
"user49": Tweet sent to 6 logged in subscribers
"user50": Logged in. Got 14 tweets.
"user50": Tweet sent to 5 logged in subscribers
"user51": Logged in. Got 16 tweets.
"user51": Tweet sent to 5 logged in subscribers
"user52": Logged in. Got 17 tweets.
"user52": Tweet sent to 4 logged in subscribers
"user53": Logged in. Got 19 tweets.
"user53": Tweet sent to 5 logged in subscribers
"user54": Logged in. Got 16 tweets.
"user54": Tweet sent to 4 logged in subscribers
"user55": Logged in. Got 17 tweets.
"user55": Tweet sent to 3 logged in subscribers
"user56": Logged in. Got 24 tweets.
"user56": Tweet sent to 1 logged in subscribers
"user57": Logged in. Got 21 tweets.
"user57": Tweet sent to 3 logged in subscribers
"user58": Logged in. Got 26 tweets.
"user58": Tweet sent to 3 logged in subscribers
"user59": Logged in. Got 19 tweets.
"user59": Tweet sent to 4 logged in subscribers
"user60": Logged in. Got 22 tweets.
"user60": Tweet sent to 4 logged in subscribers
"user61": Logged in. Got 15 tweets.
"user61": Tweet sent to 2 logged in subscribers
"user62": Logged in. Got 21 tweets.
"user62": Tweet sent to 4 logged in subscribers
"user63": Logged in. Got 22 tweets.
"user63": Tweet sent to 2 logged in subscribers
"user64": Logged in. Got 25 tweets.
"user64": Tweet sent to 4 logged in subscribers
"user65": Logged in. Got 22 tweets.
"user65": Tweet sent to 2 logged in subscribers
"user66": Logged in. Got 18 tweets.
"user66": Tweet sent to 4 logged in subscribers
"user67": Logged in. Got 24 tweets.
"user67": Tweet sent to 2 logged in subscribers
"user68": Logged in. Got 27 tweets.
"user68": Tweet sent to 4 logged in subscribers
"user69": Logged in. Got 12 tweets.
"user69": Tweet sent to 2 logged in subscribers
"user70": Logged in. Got 19 tweets.
"user70": Tweet sent to 1 logged in subscribers
"user71": Logged in. Got 23 tweets.
"user71": Tweet sent to 2 logged in subscribers
"user72": Logged in. Got 18 tweets.
"user72": Tweet sent to 3 logged in subscribers
"user73": Logged in. Got 17 tweets.
"user73": Tweet sent to 3 logged in subscribers
"user74": Logged in. Got 15 tweets.
"user74": Tweet sent to 2 logged in subscribers
"user75": Logged in. Got 24 tweets.
"user75": Tweet sent to 0 logged in subscribers
"user76": Logged in. Got 21 tweets.
"user76": Tweet sent to 2 logged in subscribers
"user77": Logged in. Got 12 tweets.
"user77": Tweet sent to 2 logged in subscribers
"user78": Logged in. Got 22 tweets.
"user78": Tweet sent to 2 logged in subscribers
"user79": Logged in. Got 22 tweets.
"user79": Tweet sent to 2 logged in subscribers
"user80": Logged in. Got 32 tweets.
"user80": Tweet sent to 2 logged in subscribers
"user81": Logged in. Got 22 tweets.
"user81": Tweet sent to 2 logged in subscribers
"user82": Logged in. Got 21 tweets.
"user82": Tweet sent to 1 logged in subscribers
"user83": Logged in. Got 15 tweets.
"user83": Tweet sent to 1 logged in subscribers
"user84": Logged in. Got 23 tweets.
"user84": Tweet sent to 1 logged in subscribers
"user85": Logged in. Got 18 tweets.
"user85": Tweet sent to 1 logged in subscribers
"user86": Logged in. Got 18 tweets.
"user86": Tweet sent to 1 logged in subscribers
"user87": Logged in. Got 18 tweets.
"user87": Tweet sent to 0 logged in subscribers
"user88": Logged in. Got 22 tweets.
"user88": Tweet sent to 1 logged in subscribers
"user89": Logged in. Got 21 tweets.
"user89": Tweet sent to 1 logged in subscribers
"user90": Logged in. Got 23 tweets.
"user90": Tweet sent to 1 logged in subscribers
"user91": Logged in. Got 19 tweets.
"user91": Tweet sent to 1 logged in subscribers
"user92": Logged in. Got 13 tweets.
"user92": Tweet sent to 1 logged in subscribers
"user93": Logged in. Got 27 tweets.
"user93": Tweet sent to 1 logged in subscribers
"user94": Logged in. Got 17 tweets.
"user94": Tweet sent to 1 logged in subscribers
"user95": Logged in. Got 15 tweets.
"user95": Tweet sent to 1 logged in subscribers
"user96": Logged in. Got 22 tweets.
"user96": Tweet sent to 1 logged in subscribers
"user97": Logged in. Got 25 tweets.
"user97": Tweet sent to 1 logged in subscribers
"user98": Logged in. Got 24 tweets.
"user98": Tweet sent to 1 logged in subscribers
"user99": Logged in. Got 21 tweets.
"user99": Tweet sent to 1 logged in subscribers
"user100": Logged in. Got 0 tweets.
"user100": Tweet sent to 1 logged in subscribers
"user9": Retweet sent to 79 logged in subscribers
"user8": Retweet sent to 85 logged in subscribers
"user2": Tweet sent to 95 logged in subscribers
"user5": Tweet sent to 93 logged in subscribers
"user1": Tweet sent to 97 logged in subscribers
"user4": Retweet sent to 94 logged in subscribers
"user3": Tweet sent to 94 logged in subscribers
"user11": Retweet sent to 61 logged in subscribers
"user12": Retweet sent to 59 logged in subscribers
"user10": Tweet sent to 75 logged in subscribers
"user6": Tweet sent to 92 logged in subscribers
"user7": Retweet sent to 91 logged in subscribers
"user14": Retweet sent to 52 logged in subscribers
"user15": Retweet sent to 49 logged in subscribers
"user16": Retweet sent to 42 logged in subscribers
"user17": Tweet sent to 42 logged in subscribers
"user18": Tweet sent to 41 logged in subscribers
"user19": Tweet sent to 39 logged in subscribers
"user20": Tweet sent to 31 logged in subscribers
"user21": Tweet sent to 29 logged in subscribers
"user22": Retweet sent to 28 logged in subscribers
"user23": Tweet sent to 26 logged in subscribers
"user25": Retweet sent to 26 logged in subscribers
"user26": Retweet sent to 24 logged in subscribers
"user27": Retweet sent to 21 logged in subscribers
"user24": Retweet sent to 26 logged in subscribers
"user28": Tweet sent to 20 logged in subscribers
"user29": Tweet sent to 20 logged in subscribers
"user30": Tweet sent to 19 logged in subscribers
"user31": Tweet sent to 18 logged in subscribers
"user32": Tweet sent to 17 logged in subscribers
"user33": Tweet sent to 15 logged in subscribers
"user34": Tweet sent to 15 logged in subscribers
"user35": Tweet sent to 14 logged in subscribers
"user36": Retweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user37": Tweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user13": Retweet sent to 54 logged in subscribers
"user38": Retweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user39": Tweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user42": Tweet sent to 11 logged in subscribers
"user43": Tweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user44": Retweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user41": Tweet sent to 12 logged in subscribers
"user45": Tweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user46": Tweet sent to 9 logged in subscribers
"user40": Tweet sent to 12 logged in subscribers
"user47": Retweet sent to 9 logged in subscribers
"user48": Tweet sent to 8 logged in subscribers
"user49": Tweet sent to 8 logged in subscribers
"user1": Tweet sent to 97 logged in subscribers
"user2": Tweet sent to 95 logged in subscribers
"user3": Tweet sent to 94 logged in subscribers
"user4": Retweet sent to 94 logged in subscribers
"user7": Retweet sent to 91 logged in subscribers
"user6": Retweet sent to 92 logged in subscribers
"user5": Tweet sent to 93 logged in subscribers
"user8": Tweet sent to 85 logged in subscribers
"user9": Tweet sent to 79 logged in subscribers
"user10": Tweet sent to 75 logged in subscribers
"user11": Tweet sent to 61 logged in subscribers
"user12": Tweet sent to 59 logged in subscribers
"user13": Retweet sent to 54 logged in subscribers
"user14": Tweet sent to 52 logged in subscribers
"user16": Retweet sent to 42 logged in subscribers
"user15": Retweet sent to 49 logged in subscribers
"user17": Retweet sent to 42 logged in subscribers
"user18": Tweet sent to 41 logged in subscribers
"user19": Retweet sent to 39 logged in subscribers
"user20": Tweet sent to 31 logged in subscribers
"user23": Retweet sent to 26 logged in subscribers
"user22": Retweet sent to 28 logged in subscribers
"user21": Retweet sent to 29 logged in subscribers
"user25": Tweet sent to 26 logged in subscribers
"user24": Retweet sent to 26 logged in subscribers
"user26": Tweet sent to 24 logged in subscribers
"user28": Tweet sent to 20 logged in subscribers
"user27": Tweet sent to 21 logged in subscribers
"user30": Tweet sent to 19 logged in subscribers
"user31": Retweet sent to 18 logged in subscribers
"user29": Tweet sent to 20 logged in subscribers
"user32": Retweet sent to 17 logged in subscribers
"user33": Retweet sent to 15 logged in subscribers
"user35": Retweet sent to 14 logged in subscribers
"user34": Retweet sent to 15 logged in subscribers
"user37": Tweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user38": Retweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user36": Tweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user39": Tweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user41": Retweet sent to 12 logged in subscribers
"user43": Tweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user42": Tweet sent to 11 logged in subscribers
"user44": Tweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user40": Tweet sent to 12 logged in subscribers
"user45": Tweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user46": Tweet sent to 9 logged in subscribers
"user47": Tweet sent to 9 logged in subscribers
"user49": Tweet sent to 8 logged in subscribers
"user48": Tweet sent to 8 logged in subscribers
"user1": Retweet sent to 97 logged in subscribers
"user2": Retweet sent to 95 logged in subscribers
"user4": Retweet sent to 94 logged in subscribers
"user3": Tweet sent to 94 logged in subscribers
"user5": Tweet sent to 93 logged in subscribers
"user6": Tweet sent to 92 logged in subscribers
"user7": Tweet sent to 91 logged in subscribers
"user9": Retweet sent to 79 logged in subscribers
"user11": Tweet sent to 61 logged in subscribers
"user12": Retweet sent to 59 logged in subscribers
"user13": Tweet sent to 54 logged in subscribers
"user10": Retweet sent to 75 logged in subscribers
"user14": Tweet sent to 52 logged in subscribers
"user16": Tweet sent to 42 logged in subscribers
"user15": Tweet sent to 49 logged in subscribers
"user18": Tweet sent to 41 logged in subscribers
"user19": Retweet sent to 39 logged in subscribers
"user20": Tweet sent to 31 logged in subscribers
"user21": Retweet sent to 29 logged in subscribers
"user22": Tweet sent to 28 logged in subscribers
"user23": Retweet sent to 26 logged in subscribers
"user24": Retweet sent to 26 logged in subscribers
"user25": Tweet sent to 26 logged in subscribers
"user26": Tweet sent to 24 logged in subscribers
"user27": Retweet sent to 21 logged in subscribers
"user8": Retweet sent to 85 logged in subscribers
"user28": Tweet sent to 20 logged in subscribers
"user30": Tweet sent to 19 logged in subscribers
"user29": Retweet sent to 20 logged in subscribers
"user32": Retweet sent to 17 logged in subscribers
"user31": Retweet sent to 18 logged in subscribers
"user33": Tweet sent to 15 logged in subscribers
"user34": Tweet sent to 15 logged in subscribers
"user35": Tweet sent to 14 logged in subscribers
"user36": Tweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user37": Retweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user38": Retweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user39": Retweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user40": Tweet sent to 12 logged in subscribers
"user41": Retweet sent to 12 logged in subscribers
"user42": Retweet sent to 11 logged in subscribers
"user43": Tweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user44": Tweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user45": Tweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user46": Retweet sent to 9 logged in subscribers
"user47": Tweet sent to 9 logged in subscribers
"user48": Tweet sent to 8 logged in subscribers
"user49": Tweet sent to 8 logged in subscribers
"user17": Tweet sent to 42 logged in subscribers
"user2": Tweet sent to 95 logged in subscribers
"user1": Tweet sent to 97 logged in subscribers
"user4": Tweet sent to 94 logged in subscribers
"user3": Retweet sent to 94 logged in subscribers
"user5": Tweet sent to 93 logged in subscribers
"user6": Tweet sent to 92 logged in subscribers
"user7": Retweet sent to 91 logged in subscribers
"user8": Retweet sent to 85 logged in subscribers
"user9": Tweet sent to 79 logged in subscribers
"user10": Tweet sent to 75 logged in subscribers
"user12": Tweet sent to 59 logged in subscribers
"user11": Tweet sent to 61 logged in subscribers
"user13": Retweet sent to 54 logged in subscribers
"user14": Retweet sent to 52 logged in subscribers
"user16": Tweet sent to 42 logged in subscribers
"user15": Tweet sent to 49 logged in subscribers
"user17": Tweet sent to 42 logged in subscribers
"user18": Tweet sent to 41 logged in subscribers
"user19": Retweet sent to 39 logged in subscribers
"user20": Tweet sent to 31 logged in subscribers
"user21": Retweet sent to 29 logged in subscribers
"user22": Tweet sent to 28 logged in subscribers
"user23": Retweet sent to 26 logged in subscribers
"user24": Retweet sent to 26 logged in subscribers
"user25": Tweet sent to 26 logged in subscribers
"user26": Tweet sent to 24 logged in subscribers
"user27": Tweet sent to 21 logged in subscribers
"user28": Retweet sent to 20 logged in subscribers
"user29": Tweet sent to 20 logged in subscribers
"user30": Tweet sent to 19 logged in subscribers
"user31": Retweet sent to 18 logged in subscribers
"user34": Tweet sent to 15 logged in subscribers
"user33": Retweet sent to 15 logged in subscribers
"user32": Tweet sent to 17 logged in subscribers
"user37": Tweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user38": Tweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user35": Retweet sent to 14 logged in subscribers
"user36": Retweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user39": Tweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user40": Tweet sent to 12 logged in subscribers
"user41": Tweet sent to 12 logged in subscribers
"user42": Tweet sent to 11 logged in subscribers
"user44": Retweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user45": Retweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user46": Tweet sent to 9 logged in subscribers
"user43": Retweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user48": Tweet sent to 8 logged in subscribers
"user47": Tweet sent to 9 logged in subscribers
"user49": Retweet sent to 8 logged in subscribers
"user1": Tweet sent to 97 logged in subscribers
"user3": Retweet sent to 94 logged in subscribers
"user2": Retweet sent to 95 logged in subscribers
"user4": Retweet sent to 94 logged in subscribers
"user5": Retweet sent to 93 logged in subscribers
"user7": Tweet sent to 91 logged in subscribers
"user6": Tweet sent to 92 logged in subscribers
"user8": Retweet sent to 85 logged in subscribers
"user11": Retweet sent to 61 logged in subscribers
"user9": Tweet sent to 79 logged in subscribers
"user12": Tweet sent to 59 logged in subscribers
"user13": Tweet sent to 54 logged in subscribers
"user14": Tweet sent to 52 logged in subscribers
"user15": Tweet sent to 49 logged in subscribers
"user16": Retweet sent to 42 logged in subscribers
"user17": Tweet sent to 42 logged in subscribers
"user18": Tweet sent to 41 logged in subscribers
"user24": Retweet sent to 26 logged in subscribers
"user20": Retweet sent to 31 logged in subscribers
"user21": Retweet sent to 29 logged in subscribers
"user22": Tweet sent to 28 logged in subscribers
"user19": Tweet sent to 39 logged in subscribers
"user23": Retweet sent to 26 logged in subscribers
"user36": Retweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user25": Tweet sent to 26 logged in subscribers
"user27": Tweet sent to 21 logged in subscribers
"user26": Retweet sent to 24 logged in subscribers
"user28": Retweet sent to 20 logged in subscribers
"user29": Retweet sent to 20 logged in subscribers
"user30": Tweet sent to 19 logged in subscribers
"user31": Tweet sent to 18 logged in subscribers
"user34": Tweet sent to 15 logged in subscribers
"user35": Tweet sent to 14 logged in subscribers
"user33": Tweet sent to 15 logged in subscribers
"user37": Tweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user38": Tweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user39": Tweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user40": Retweet sent to 12 logged in subscribers
"user41": Tweet sent to 12 logged in subscribers
"user42": Retweet sent to 11 logged in subscribers
"user43": Tweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user44": Retweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user45": Tweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user46": Tweet sent to 9 logged in subscribers
"user48": Tweet sent to 8 logged in subscribers
"user49": Retweet sent to 8 logged in subscribers
"user47": Tweet sent to 9 logged in subscribers
"user32": Retweet sent to 17 logged in subscribers
"user10": Tweet sent to 75 logged in subscribers
"user4": Retweet sent to 94 logged in subscribers
"user2": Retweet sent to 95 logged in subscribers
"user5": Tweet sent to 93 logged in subscribers
"user7": Tweet sent to 91 logged in subscribers
"user6": Tweet sent to 92 logged in subscribers
"user8": Tweet sent to 85 logged in subscribers
"user9": Tweet sent to 79 logged in subscribers
"user1": Tweet sent to 97 logged in subscribers
"user10": Retweet sent to 75 logged in subscribers
"user12": Tweet sent to 59 logged in subscribers
"user11": Retweet sent to 61 logged in subscribers
"user13": Retweet sent to 54 logged in subscribers
"user14": Retweet sent to 52 logged in subscribers
"user15": Retweet sent to 49 logged in subscribers
"user17": Tweet sent to 42 logged in subscribers
"user16": Tweet sent to 42 logged in subscribers
"user18": Retweet sent to 41 logged in subscribers
"user19": Tweet sent to 39 logged in subscribers
"user20": Tweet sent to 31 logged in subscribers
"user22": Retweet sent to 28 logged in subscribers
"user21": Tweet sent to 29 logged in subscribers
"user23": Tweet sent to 26 logged in subscribers
"user24": Retweet sent to 26 logged in subscribers
"user26": Tweet sent to 24 logged in subscribers
"user25": Retweet sent to 26 logged in subscribers
"user27": Retweet sent to 21 logged in subscribers
"user28": Tweet sent to 20 logged in subscribers
"user30": Tweet sent to 19 logged in subscribers
"user31": Tweet sent to 18 logged in subscribers
"user32": Retweet sent to 17 logged in subscribers
"user29": Retweet sent to 20 logged in subscribers
"user33": Tweet sent to 15 logged in subscribers
"user3": Tweet sent to 94 logged in subscribers
"user34": Retweet sent to 15 logged in subscribers
"user35": Tweet sent to 14 logged in subscribers
"user37": Retweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user36": Retweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user39": Tweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user40": Retweet sent to 12 logged in subscribers
"user42": Tweet sent to 11 logged in subscribers
"user38": Tweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user41": Tweet sent to 12 logged in subscribers
"user43": Retweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user45": Tweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user44": Retweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user46": Retweet sent to 9 logged in subscribers
"user47": Retweet sent to 9 logged in subscribers
"user49": Retweet sent to 8 logged in subscribers
"user48": Retweet sent to 8 logged in subscribers
"user1": Tweet sent to 97 logged in subscribers
"user4": Tweet sent to 94 logged in subscribers
"user2": Tweet sent to 95 logged in subscribers
"user3": Tweet sent to 94 logged in subscribers
"user5": Tweet sent to 93 logged in subscribers
"user6": Tweet sent to 92 logged in subscribers
"user7": Tweet sent to 91 logged in subscribers
"user8": Tweet sent to 85 logged in subscribers
"user9": Retweet sent to 79 logged in subscribers
"user11": Tweet sent to 61 logged in subscribers
"user10": Tweet sent to 75 logged in subscribers
"user12": Retweet sent to 59 logged in subscribers
"user13": Tweet sent to 54 logged in subscribers
"user15": Retweet sent to 49 logged in subscribers
"user14": Tweet sent to 52 logged in subscribers
"user16": Retweet sent to 42 logged in subscribers
"user17": Tweet sent to 42 logged in subscribers
"user18": Tweet sent to 41 logged in subscribers
"user19": Retweet sent to 39 logged in subscribers
"user20": Tweet sent to 31 logged in subscribers
"user22": Retweet sent to 28 logged in subscribers
"user23": Retweet sent to 26 logged in subscribers
"user21": Tweet sent to 29 logged in subscribers
"user24": Retweet sent to 26 logged in subscribers
"user25": Retweet sent to 26 logged in subscribers
"user26": Tweet sent to 24 logged in subscribers
"user27": Tweet sent to 21 logged in subscribers
"user29": Tweet sent to 20 logged in subscribers
"user28": Retweet sent to 20 logged in subscribers
"user30": Tweet sent to 19 logged in subscribers
"user32": Tweet sent to 17 logged in subscribers
"user31": Retweet sent to 18 logged in subscribers
"user33": Tweet sent to 15 logged in subscribers
"user35": Retweet sent to 14 logged in subscribers
"user34": Retweet sent to 15 logged in subscribers
"user36": Tweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user38": Tweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user37": Retweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user39": Retweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user40": Tweet sent to 12 logged in subscribers
"user41": Tweet sent to 12 logged in subscribers
"user43": Tweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user42": Tweet sent to 11 logged in subscribers
"user44": Tweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user45": Tweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user46": Tweet sent to 9 logged in subscribers
"user47": Tweet sent to 9 logged in subscribers
"user48": Retweet sent to 8 logged in subscribers
"user49": Retweet sent to 8 logged in subscribers
"user4": Tweet sent to 94 logged in subscribers
"user3": Tweet sent to 94 logged in subscribers
"user1": Retweet sent to 97 logged in subscribers
"user5": Retweet sent to 93 logged in subscribers
"user6": Retweet sent to 92 logged in subscribers
"user7": Tweet sent to 91 logged in subscribers
"user10": Tweet sent to 75 logged in subscribers
"user8": Tweet sent to 85 logged in subscribers
"user11": Tweet sent to 61 logged in subscribers
"user12": Retweet sent to 59 logged in subscribers
"user13": Tweet sent to 54 logged in subscribers
"user9": Retweet sent to 79 logged in subscribers
"user14": Retweet sent to 52 logged in subscribers
"user15": Tweet sent to 49 logged in subscribers
"user18": Tweet sent to 41 logged in subscribers
"user16": Tweet sent to 42 logged in subscribers
"user17": Tweet sent to 42 logged in subscribers
"user19": Tweet sent to 39 logged in subscribers
"user21": Retweet sent to 29 logged in subscribers
"user22": Tweet sent to 28 logged in subscribers
"user23": Tweet sent to 26 logged in subscribers
"user24": Tweet sent to 26 logged in subscribers
"user20": Retweet sent to 31 logged in subscribers
"user27": Tweet sent to 21 logged in subscribers
"user26": Tweet sent to 24 logged in subscribers
"user28": Retweet sent to 20 logged in subscribers
"user25": Retweet sent to 26 logged in subscribers
"user29": Retweet sent to 20 logged in subscribers
"user31": Retweet sent to 18 logged in subscribers
"user30": Tweet sent to 19 logged in subscribers
"user32": Retweet sent to 17 logged in subscribers
"user33": Retweet sent to 15 logged in subscribers
"user35": Tweet sent to 14 logged in subscribers
"user36": Tweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user38": Retweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user37": Tweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user34": Retweet sent to 15 logged in subscribers
"user40": Tweet sent to 12 logged in subscribers
"user39": Tweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user42": Tweet sent to 11 logged in subscribers
"user43": Tweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user41": Retweet sent to 12 logged in subscribers
"user44": Retweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user45": Tweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user46": Tweet sent to 9 logged in subscribers
"user47": Tweet sent to 9 logged in subscribers
"user49": Retweet sent to 8 logged in subscribers
"user48": Retweet sent to 8 logged in subscribers
"user2": Retweet sent to 95 logged in subscribers
"user1": Retweet sent to 97 logged in subscribers
"user2": Retweet sent to 95 logged in subscribers
"user3": Tweet sent to 94 logged in subscribers
"user4": Tweet sent to 94 logged in subscribers
"user5": Tweet sent to 93 logged in subscribers
"user6": Tweet sent to 92 logged in subscribers
"user7": Tweet sent to 91 logged in subscribers
"user8": Tweet sent to 85 logged in subscribers
"user9": Tweet sent to 79 logged in subscribers
"user10": Tweet sent to 75 logged in subscribers
"user11": Retweet sent to 61 logged in subscribers
"user12": Tweet sent to 59 logged in subscribers
"user13": Tweet sent to 54 logged in subscribers
"user14": Tweet sent to 52 logged in subscribers
"user15": Tweet sent to 49 logged in subscribers
"user16": Retweet sent to 42 logged in subscribers
"user17": Retweet sent to 42 logged in subscribers
"user18": Tweet sent to 41 logged in subscribers
"user19": Tweet sent to 39 logged in subscribers
"user20": Tweet sent to 31 logged in subscribers
"user21": Tweet sent to 29 logged in subscribers
"user22": Tweet sent to 28 logged in subscribers
"user23": Retweet sent to 26 logged in subscribers
"user24": Retweet sent to 26 logged in subscribers
"user25": Retweet sent to 26 logged in subscribers
"user26": Tweet sent to 24 logged in subscribers
"user27": Tweet sent to 21 logged in subscribers
"user28": Retweet sent to 20 logged in subscribers
"user29": Tweet sent to 20 logged in subscribers
"user30": Retweet sent to 19 logged in subscribers
"user31": Tweet sent to 18 logged in subscribers
"user32": Tweet sent to 17 logged in subscribers
"user34": Tweet sent to 15 logged in subscribers
"user33": Retweet sent to 15 logged in subscribers
"user35": Retweet sent to 14 logged in subscribers
"user36": Retweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user37": Tweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user38": Tweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user40": Retweet sent to 12 logged in subscribers
"user39": Retweet sent to 13 logged in subscribers
"user42": Tweet sent to 11 logged in subscribers
"user41": Retweet sent to 12 logged in subscribers
"user43": Retweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user44": Tweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user46": Retweet sent to 9 logged in subscribers
"user45": Retweet sent to 10 logged in subscribers
"user47": Tweet sent to 9 logged in subscribers
"user48": Retweet sent to 8 logged in subscribers
"user49": Retweet sent to 8 logged in subscribers
"user100": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30004 milliseconds
"user1": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31710 milliseconds
"user3": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31688 milliseconds
"user4": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31673 milliseconds
"user6": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31641 milliseconds
"user5": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31657 milliseconds
"user2": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31705 milliseconds
"user7": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31626 milliseconds
"user8": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31610 milliseconds
"user10": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31577 milliseconds
"user9": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31593 milliseconds
"user11": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31561 milliseconds
"user13": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31514 milliseconds
"user14": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31512 milliseconds
"user15": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31498 milliseconds
"user12": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31545 milliseconds
"user16": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31483 milliseconds
"user17": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31468 milliseconds
"user18": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31452 milliseconds
"user19": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31436 milliseconds
"user20": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31419 milliseconds
"user21": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31404 milliseconds
"user22": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31389 milliseconds
"user23": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31374 milliseconds
"user24": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31358 milliseconds
"user25": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31342 milliseconds
"user26": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31326 milliseconds
"user27": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31310 milliseconds
"user28": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31294 milliseconds
"user30": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31263 milliseconds
"user29": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31279 milliseconds
"user32": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31231 milliseconds
"user31": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31247 milliseconds
"user33": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31216 milliseconds
"user34": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31200 milliseconds
"user36": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31169 milliseconds
"user35": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31185 milliseconds
"user38": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31137 milliseconds
"user37": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31153 milliseconds
"user39": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31121 milliseconds
"user40": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31105 milliseconds
"user41": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31089 milliseconds
"user43": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31058 milliseconds
"user42": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31073 milliseconds
"user44": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31040 milliseconds
"user45": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31025 milliseconds
"user46": Logged Out. Log Session time is 31010 milliseconds
"user48": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30976 milliseconds
"user47": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30993 milliseconds
"user49": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30961 milliseconds
"user50": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30945 milliseconds
"user51": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30930 milliseconds
"user52": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30914 milliseconds
"user53": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30897 milliseconds
"user54": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30885 milliseconds
"user55": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30869 milliseconds
"user57": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30837 milliseconds
"user56": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30853 milliseconds
"user58": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30821 milliseconds
"user59": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30806 milliseconds
"user60": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30789 milliseconds
"user62": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30759 milliseconds
"user61": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30775 milliseconds
"user63": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30743 milliseconds
"user65": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30712 milliseconds
"user64": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30727 milliseconds
"user66": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30695 milliseconds
"user70": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30632 milliseconds
"user69": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30648 milliseconds
"user67": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30680 milliseconds
"user71": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30616 milliseconds
"user68": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30663 milliseconds
"user72": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30599 milliseconds
"user73": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30584 milliseconds
"user74": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30564 milliseconds
"user75": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30550 milliseconds
"user76": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30537 milliseconds
"user77": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30522 milliseconds
"user78": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30505 milliseconds
"user80": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30474 milliseconds
"user79": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30489 milliseconds
"user81": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30457 milliseconds
"user82": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30442 milliseconds
"user83": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30426 milliseconds
"user84": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30410 milliseconds
"user85": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30394 milliseconds
"user86": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30378 milliseconds
"user88": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30344 milliseconds
"user87": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30362 milliseconds
"user89": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30332 milliseconds
"user90": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30315 milliseconds
"user91": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30300 milliseconds
"user93": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30266 milliseconds
"user92": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30283 milliseconds
"user96": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30221 milliseconds
"user94": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30254 milliseconds
"user95": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30238 milliseconds
"user97": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30206 milliseconds
"user98": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30189 milliseconds
"user99": Logged Out. Log Session time is 30173 milliseconds
************************************************************************************
Real: 00:00:32.826, CPU: 00:00:02.296, GC gen0: 58, gen1: 7, gen2: 0
************************************************************************************
Total users logged to server: 100
Total number of tweets sent by users: 541
Expected number of tweets to be received by users: 18488
Number of tweets received to logged users: 16885
